A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.3-SG 1.8 (A76-A82) FA209
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.3-SG 1.8 (A76-A82)
1944-2002
undated
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA209
573.88 Cubic Feet 1517 containers
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Rockefeller Foundation photographs, special formats and closed material have been relocated to the end of each Project File Subgroup.
Medical care; Public health administration; Malaria; Hookworm disease; Scarlatina -- Hospitals -- Administration; Social sciences -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Nursing; Natural history; Agriculture; Medical sciences; Scholarships; Public health; Public health -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Humanities -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Life sciences; Social sciences; Arts; Yaws; Viruses -- Research; Philanthropy; Humanities; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Epidemiology; Tuberculosis; Philanthropy -- United States; Charities; Public health -- Education; War relief; Yellow fever; Epidemics; Hospitals
- Projects (A76), before 1975; 3; 48.16 Cubic Feet 173 containers; Document boxes 1-130.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Files transferred to RAC by the Rockefeller Foundation, 1976-January 1977.
  Photographs and Closed Material
  Rockefeller Foundation photographs and closed material have been relocated to the end of each Project File Subgroup.
  Arrangement
  Records are primarily arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
  Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
  - International, 100; 1 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes and 1 half-legal box
    - International - Medical Sciences, 100A
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Planning Family, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Planning Family, 1971 April-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Planning Family, 1972 Jan.-June (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Planning Family, 1972 July-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Planning Family, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Planning Family - Supplementary Material, 1971-1972; Internal Document, University of Costa Rica 1971 Proposal to Establish a Regional Center for Training Family Planning Communicators in Latin America (Addressed to: Ford Foundation and International Planned Parenthood Federation, Western Hemisfere Region) The Victor-Bostrom Fund for the International Planned Parenthood Federation, Report No. 15, Winter 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Planning Family - Supplementary Material, 1972-1974; OVERVIEW 1972 Medical and Clinical Activities Family Planning Associations Western Hemisphere Region Draft, Work Programme IPPH 1972-1974 Presented by the Secretary General (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Planning Family - Supplementary Material, 1974; FPIA Brochure and Annual Report for Program year 3 and Proposal for Program year 4 Section V: Project Narratives organized by region (pages 107-274) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - International - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 100D
      - International Sorghum and Millets, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - International Sorghum and Millets, 1969 Jan.-Aug. (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - International Sorghum and Millets, 1969 Aug.-Dec. (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - International Sorghum and Millets, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - International Sorghum and Millets, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center, 105; 6.59 Cubic Feet 19 containers
    - Administration, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Administration, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Agreements, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Agreements, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Agricultural Journal Lists, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors, 1969 Jan.-Oct. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors - Supplementary Material, 1969 Sept.; IMWIC Clippings IV Meeting of the Board of Directors (Spanish) IMWIC Agenda IV Meeting of the Board of Directors (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Daylength Insensitivity, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Separated Materials
      Photographs and special formats relocated to box 130A
    - Donation of Equipment, 1968-1971, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Financial, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Financial, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Financial - Supplementay Material, 1967-1969; 1969 Proposed CIMMYT Budget; IMWIC Program Staff and Proposed Budget Requirements for 1968 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Financial - Agency for the International Development, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Genetic Improvement, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Germplasm Meetings, 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Grain Production, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Headquarters Development, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Headquarters Development, 1970 Jan.-March (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Headquarters Development, 1970 March (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Headquarters Development, 1970 April-Oct. (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Headquarters Development, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Headquarters Development, 1971 April-Dec. (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Headquarters Development, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Headquarters Development - Supplementary Material, 1969-1971; Clarifications, explainations and Instuctions to consultants and to La Partida IX "Unidades De Iluminacion" CIMMYT (Spanish) (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Headquarters Development - Greenhouses, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Headquarters Inauguration, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Headquarters Inauguration, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Maize Consultants, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Organization and Planning, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Organization and Planning, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Organization and Planning, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Protein Laboratory, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Protein Laboratory, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Protein Laboratory, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Publicity and Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Publicity and Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1965-1967; Research Bulletin No. 1 Chromosome Morphology of Certain Races of Maize in Latin America 1966-67 Report CIMMYT (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1967-1968; Research Bulletin No. 6 February 1967, Meejoramiento Genetico del Anfiploide Triticale Research Bulletin No. 7 March 1967, Results of the Fourth Inter-American Spring Wheat Yield Nursery 1963-1964 Research Bulletin N0. 3 July 1967, Hybrid Wheats: Their Development and Food Potential CIMMYT Report: on Progress toward increasing yields of maize and Wheat 1967-68 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1968; Research Bulletin No. 8 March 1968, Results of the First International Spring Wheat Yield Nursery 1964-1965 Research Bulletin No. 10 July 1968, Variability in the Lysine Content of Rye, and Triticales Proteins Research Bulletin No. 11 August 1968, Results of the Second International Spring Wheat Yield Nursery, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1968-1971; Research Bulletin No. 9 March 1968, Field Technoque for Fertilizer Experiments Research Bulletin No. 12 February 1969, Combining data from Fertilizer experiments into a function useful for establishing specific fertilizer recommendations Research Bulletin No. 13 May 1969, A Modified Method for Rapid Tryptophan Analysis of Maize Research Bulletin No. 16 August 1979, Results of the First and Second International Screening Nurseries 1967-1969 Brochure, CIMMYT Purpose Organization and Programs 1970-71 Repot\rt on Maize and Wheat Improvement (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1971 Feb.-March; Research Bulletin No. 17 February 1971, Progress in Developing Triticales as an Economic Crop Research Bulletin No. 18 February 1971, Results of the Fourth International Spring Yield Nursery, 1967-1968 Research Bulletin No. 19 March 1971, Results of the Fifth International Spring Wheat Yield Nursery, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1971 May-June; Research Bulletin No. 22 June 1971, Results of the Third International Bread Wheat Screening Nurseries (Series A and B) 1969-1970 Research Bulletin No. 21 May 1971, A Survey on Leaf Rust Resistance in the USDA World Durum Collection Research Bulletin No. 20 June 1971, Chemical Screening Methods for Maize Protein Quality at CIMMYT (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1972; List of Participants Program Dec. 4-8, 1972 What Is CIMMYT ? March 1972 CIMMYT (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1973 March-July; PCCMCA XIX Reunion, San Jose, Costa Rica March 4-8, 1973 (Spanish) UNDP Global Research July 10, 1973 Final Report covering the period March 1970-March 1973 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1973-1974; CIMMYT Resident Maize Program 1973-74, Reserach Bulletin No. 25 October 1973, Results of the Seventh International Spring Wheat Yield Nursery 1970-1971 CIMMYT Research Bulletin No. 27 January, 1974, Epidemiology of Whweat Rusts in the Western Hemisphere (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1974 April; World-Wide Maize Improvement in the 70's and the Role for CIMMYT April 22-26, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1975; Maize Program, 1975, Preliminary Report, International Progeny Testing Trials and Experimental Variety Trials This Is CIMMYT (Pamphlet) CIMMYT Review 1975 Information Bulletin No. 17, March 1975 Summaries of the Fourth "A" and "B" and Fifth International Bread Wheat Screening Nurseries (IBWSN), 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplementary Material, 1976; Information Bulletin No.23, Results of the Tenth International Spring Wheat Yield Nursery (10th ISWYN), 1973-1974 Information Bulletin No.25, Results of the Sixth, Seventh and Eight International Bread Wheat Screening Nurseries (IBWSN), 1973-1975 Information Bulletin No.27, From Agronomic Data to Farmer Recommendations: An Economic Training Manual (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Tricticales, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Triticales - Supplementary Material, 1973 Nov.; Information Bulletin No. 10 November, 1973 Results of the Second and Third International Triticale Yield Nurseries 1970-71, 1971-72 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Visitors Program, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - CIMMYT - United States of America, 200
      - Washington State University - Triticales, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      - Washington State University - Triticales, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 67)
      - Washington State University - Triticales - Supplementary Material, 1972 June 5 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - CIMMYT - Argentina, 301
      - Argentina, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - CIMMYT - Colombia, 311
      - Andes, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 70)
      - Andes, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 71)
        Photographs and Special formats relocated to box 130A
    - CIMMYT - Mexico, 323
      - Graduate Studies, 1968-1973 (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - Puebla, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      - Puebla, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 74)
      - Puebla, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 75)
      - Puebla, 1970 May-Dec. (Box 14, Folder 76)
      - Puebla, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 77)
      - Puebla, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 78)
      - Puebla, 1973 Jan.-July (Box 14, Folder 79)
      - Puebla, 1973 July-Dec. (Box 14, Folder 80)
      - Puebla, 1974-1975, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 81)
      - Puebla - Supplementary Material, 1968; Proyecto Puebla, 2a Reunion Anual (Project Puebla, Second Annual Reunion) Puebla Pue., Diciebre 17 de 1968 Folder contents include Program. Work Area, Results & Advances, Production Critiera, and Evaluations & Potential Production of Maize (Box 15, Folder 82)
      - Puebla - Supplementary Material, 1969; Plan Puebla, 3a Reunion Anual, Puebla, Pue., Enero 10 de 1970 Folder contents: Program, Directors, Second Annual Recomendations, Use of Fertilizer, Technology & Production, Betterment, Importance, Results & Evaluation The Puebla Project 1967-69 (Box 15, Folder 83)
      - Puebla - Conferences, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 84)
      - Puebla - Trainees, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 85)
      - Substations, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 86)
      - Substations, 1970-1975 (Box 16, Folder 87)
      - Substations - Supplementary Material, 12/1/70; Blue Print Plans (Box 16, Folder 88)
      - Toluca Station, 1968-1972 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - CIMMYT - Paraguay, 329
      - Intergovernmental Committee for European Migration - National Wheat Program, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - CIMMYT - Canada, 427
      - Sorghum, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 91)
      - University of Manitoba - Wheat Research, 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - CIMMYT - India, 464
      - Downy Mildew - Workshop, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 93)
      - Downy Mildew - Workshop, 1969 May-Oct. (Box 17, Folder 94)
      - Downy Mildew - Workshop, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 95)
      - Wheat, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 96)
      - Wheat, 1968-1974 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - CIMMYT - Pakistan, 465
      - Wheat Improvement, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 98)
      - Wheat Improvement, 1967 June-Oct. (Box 18, Folder 99)
      - Wheat Improvement, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 100)
      - Wheat Improvement, 1968 Feb.-Dec. (Box 18, Folder 101)
      - Wheat Improvement, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - CIMMYT - Kenya, 476
      - Maize Improvement, 1963-1971 (Box 19, Folder 103-107)
    - CIMMYT - Siam (Thailand), 617
      - Granados, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 108)
      - Jinahyon, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 109)
    - CIMMYT - Belgian Congo (later Zaire), 709
      - Maize, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 110)
    - CIMMYT - Near East, 804
      - Cereal Improvement, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 111-114)
      - Wheat Improvement - Cereal Quality Lab, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 115)
      - Wheat Improvement - Cereal Quality Lab, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 116)
      - Wheat Improvement - Experimental Farm, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 117)
      - Wheat Improvement - Klatt, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 118)
  - International Potato Program (IPP), 107; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Administration, 1967-1973 (Box 22, Folder 119)
    - Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 120)
    - Financial, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 121)
    - Financial, 1969-1972 (Box 22, Folder 122)
    - Organization and Planning, 1967-1973 (Box 22, Folder 123)
    - Potato Physiology, 1971- 1975 (Box 22, Folder 125)
    - Publicity and Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 126)
    - IPP - United States of America, 200
      - University of Wisconsin - Germplasm, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 127)
      - University of Wisconsin - Germplasm, 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 128)
      - University of Wisconsin - Germplasm, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 129)
    - IPP - Philippines, 242
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 130)
    - IPP - Costa Rica, 313
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 131)
    - IPP - Mexico, 323
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 132)
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 133)
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 134)
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 135)
    - IPP - India, 464
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1967-1973 (Box 24, Folder 136)
    - IPP - Pakistan, 465
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1967-1974 (Box 24, Folder 137-140)
      - Alam, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 141)
    - IPP - Kenya, 476
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 142)
    - IPP - Near East, 804
      - International Potato Program (IPP), 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 143)
  - Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT) International Center of Tropical Agriculture, 110; 3.08 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes, 2 legal document boxes, 1 half-legal box
    - Agreements, 1966-1975 (Box 25, Folder 146-148)
    - Airplane, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 149-150)
    - Animal Science - Forage, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 151)
    - Animal Science - Forage, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 152)
    - Animal Science - Livestock Specialist Training, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 153)
    - Animal Science - Livestock Specialist Training, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 154)
    - Board of Trustees, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 155)
    - Board of Trustees, 1968 June-Dec. (Box 26, Folder 156)
    - Board of Trustees, 1969 Jan.-Dec. (Box 26, Folder 157)
    - Board of Trustees, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 158)
    - Financial, 1965-1968 (Box 27, Folder 159)
    - Financial, 1969 June-Oct. (Box 27, Folder 160)
    - Financial, 1969 Oct. (Box 27, Folder 161)
    - Financial - AID, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 162)
    - Headquarters Development, 1966-1969 (Box 27, Folder 163)
    - Headquarters Development, 1969 Aug.-Dec. (Box 28, Folder 164)
    - Headquarters Development - Supplementary Material, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 165)
    - Headquarters Development, 1971 April 8 (Box 28, Folder 166)
    - Headquarters Development - Crop Processing Plant, 1970-1975 (Box 29, Folder 167)
    - Headquarters Development - IADB, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 168)
    - Inauguration, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 169)
    - Library, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 170)
    - Library, 1968 April-June (Box 29, Folder 171)
    - Library, 1968 June-Sept. (Box 29, Folder 172)
    - Library, 1968 Sept.-Dec. (Box 29, Folder 173)
    - Library, 1969 Jan.-Oct. (Box 29, Folder 174)
    - Library, 1969-1975 (Box 30, Folder 175)
    - Nutrition Conference, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 176)
    - Organization and Planning (Box 30, Folder 177-180)
    - Publicity and Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 181)
    - Publicity and Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 182)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplemetary Material, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 183)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplemetary Material, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 184)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplemetary Material, 1971 Oct.-Dec. (Box 31, Folder 185)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplemetary Material, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 186)
    - Publicity and Reports - Supplemetary Material, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 187)
    - Turipana Station - Parasite Study, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 188)
    - CIAT - United States of America, 200
      - Cornell University - Rural Development Conference, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 189)
    - CIAT - Trinidad and Tobago, 451
      - Swine Improvement, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 190)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA), 115; 2.61 Cubic Feet
    - Administration, 1965-1969 (Box 32, Folder 191-195)
    - Board of Trustees, 1965-1970 (Box 33, Folder 196)
    - Construction and Engineering, 1965-1970 (Box 33, Folder 197)
    - Financial, 1965-1969 (Box 33, Folder 198-199, Box 34, Folder 200-204)
    - Library, 1965-1975 (Box 34, Folder 205-206)
    - Organization and Planning, 1963-1969 (Box 35, Folder 207-210, Box 36, Folder 211-213, Box 37, Folder 214-218)
    - Organization and Planning - Supplementary Material, 1965-1968 (Box 37, Folder 219-220)
    - Program Review Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 221)
    - Publicity and Reports and Supplementary Material, 1970-1976 (Box 38, Folder 222)
      Scope and Contents note
      see 242 D.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 5.32 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes
    - American Society of International Law - Individual Rights Conference, 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 223)
    - Chemical and Non-disease specific Drug Implications Conference, 1939, 1971-1973 (Box 38, Folder 224)
    - Columbia University - Nature of Man conference, 1971-1973 (Box 38, Folder 225)
    - 1973 Aug.-Nov. (Box 38, Folder 226)
    - Council on Foreign Relations - Hungarian-America Relationships Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 227)
    - Cultural Relations for the Future - Conference, 1969-1976 (Box 38, Folder 228-229)
    - Duke University - Economics Conference, 1970-1973 (Box 39, Folder 230)
    - Economic Development Manual - Conference, 1972-1975 (Box 39, Folder 231)
    - Editing Methods and Problems - Conference, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 232)
    - Geneva Graduate Institute of International Studies - Liberation movement Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 233)
    - Geneva Graduate Institute of International Studies - Multilateralism Conference, 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 234)
    - International Criminal Law Conference, 1970-1973 (Box 39, Folder 235-236)
    - International Dispute Negotiation Improvement Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 237)
    - International Economics History Association Conference, 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 238)
    - International Organization for the Study of Group Tensions Conference, 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 239)
    - International Studies Association European Perspective Conference, 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 240)
    - Kaiser Foundation International Health Care Conference, 1970-1973 (Box 40, Folder 241)
    - Literary History Theory Conference, 1972-1976 (Box 40, Folder 242)
    - Machine Intelligence Conference, 1970-1973 (Box 40, Folder 243)
    - Macy Foundation - Medical Education Conference, 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 244)
    - National Academy of Sciences - African Agriculture Conference, 1971-1974 (Box 41, Folder 245-247)
    - National Academy of Sciences - African Agriculture Conference - Supplementary Material, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 248)
    - Nobel Foundation Conference, 1969-1972 (Box 41, Folder 249, Box 42, Folder 250-253)
    - Nobel Foundation Conference - Supplementary Material, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 254-255)
    - North Atlantic Assembly - Committee of Nine Conference, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 256)
    - Race Relations and Employment Conference, 1971-1973, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 257)
    - Reduction in Biology Conference, 1970-1975 (Box 42, Folder 258)
    - Rural Unemployment in Tropical Africa Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 259)
    - Scholars - Almond, G. A., 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 260)
    - Scholars - Arendt, Hannah, 1971-1972, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 261)
    - Scholars - Ashby Eric, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 262)
    - Scholars - Asher, R. F., 1972-1973, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 263)
    - Scholars - Bachmann, Haus, 1972-1975 (Box 43, Folder 264)
    - Scholars - Baker, Carlos, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 265)
    - Scholars - Bauer, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 266)